

NỀN TẢNG TUYỂN DỤNG NHÂN SỰ HÀNG ĐẦU VIỆT NAM

Ứng viên NGUYEN VAN HUY | Nguồn tuyendung.topcv.vn





NGUYEN VAN HUY

Date of birth: June 2, 1994 Phone: +84352006910 Email: nhuy387@gmail.com Address: Da Nang, Vietnam

Website: https://www.linkedin.com/in/huy-nguyen-498873148

EDUCATION

Hue Science of University

Bachelor's degree, Information Technology

2012 - 2016

PERSONAL STATEMENT

After graduate from Hue Science University, I have undertaken several internships within leading organisations in Da Nang such as FPT Software and Asian Tech. These placements have enabled me to develop not only specific technical experience, but also a valuable and transferable skill set in this fast-paced sector such as teamwork, research skill,...

During placement with Asian Tech, I worked in the contributing and maintain projects – such as backend side and fontend side, Utilising communication skills and Scrum is an agile framework I developed and maintained successful working relationships with both colleagues and client.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Tomosia Co., Ltd.

Web Software Developer

Participate in the company's product project as a full stack website developer. Building and developing new feature for customers from the Japan. tuyendung.topcv.v

- * Main responsibilities:
- Working with Ruby, Javascript
- Deploy and release products on PROD

Asian Tech Co., Ltd.

Web Software Developer

- * Main responsibilities:
- Working with Ruby, Node, Javascript, Java
- Develop with ROR, React, Angular, Spring Boot framework
- Using deploy tools as Docker, Docker, Travis CI
- Unit testing
- * Recognition and Gains:
- Improve skill both server side and client
- How to config new project and deploy Web Application
- Scrum is an agile framework
- Knowledgeable about AWS such as EC2, S3, IAM, VPC network, CDN

Mar 2020 - Present

Mar 2017 - Feb 2020

FPT Internship

Beginning as Internship in 3 months, learning about Java, Java Struts 1.x, Coding Conventions, Testing follow procedure of FSOFT

- * Improve Skills:
- Improve communicating skills, teamwork ability
- Learn OOP, MVC pattern

